maxon.net 2010-06-13

# MAXON: Privacy Policy

**Online Privacy Practices**  
At MAXON, we take great care to safeguard your privacy. The information that we collect from you will only be used lawfully, in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998 and, as far as applicable, in accordance with the German data protection law (Bundesdatenschutzgesetz) in its valid version. We strictly adhere to the following guidelines to ensure that your details remain confidential. **

Subscription and Registration

**  
Occasionally, such as before you download our demo software, we may ask you to fill in personal information. If you do not wish to provide the information requested or receive information about our services, please [contact us](http://www.maxon.net/about/about-maxon/contact-addresses.html "Öffnet internen Link im aktuellen Fenster"). 

The information we request will often include your name, email address and other information that is usually required in order for you to register for or subscribe to our services or offers. We will not collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent. In the case of press mailings or mailing lists, you can choose to unsubscribe at any time. 

We will keep your information confidential at all times and use it solely to enhance customer service. This may occasionally include passing on your contact information to MAXON sales representatives and authorized resellers of MAXON products. However, we will not pass on your personal information to any outside organizations that have no direct affiliation with MAXON. **

Internet Commerce

**  
Our online store is designed to protect your credit card information, name, address, email and any other information that you provide to us. We offer industry-standard security measures via SSL encryption. Our servers are located in the United States of America and all order information is transferred using 128-bit SSL encryption. The personal information which we hold will be held securely, in accordance with our internal security policy and applicable laws. If at any time you would like to make a purchase but would prefer to give your credit card or purchase order information to a MAXON representative personally over the telephone, you may do so. Simply call or write to your nearest authorized MAXON distributor. 

It is MAXON's policy to contact you should difficulties arise with your purchase. We make every effort to ensure that our information about you is kept accurate and up to date. If you would like to check this information, please email us and we will promptly correct or delete any inaccuracies. Our information about you will be kept confidential and will be used solely to enhance your relationship with MAXON as a valued customer. We will not pass on your personal information to any outside organizations. **

Customized Experience

**  
Internet technologies such as cookies enable us to customize and enhance your visits to the MAXON website. For example, cookies may tell us which type of computer you are using, and thus which services may be of interest to you. Be assured that we use this technology for the sole purpose of better serving you. MAXON has no desire or intent to infringe upon your privacy. We hope you will enjoy using our Internet services. 

MAXON reserves the right to make modifications, deletions, or additions without notice. 

Copyright 1998-2009, MAXON Computer GmbH, MAXON Computer Inc., MAXON Computer Ltd. 

All rights reserved.
